Review exercise 15, Ignorance on Parade. Now, let's dissect the standard paragraph,
including its title, as we did in review exercise 1. First, in the blue phrases in
the first paragraph, decide which is a descriptive phrase, which is a set phrase,
and where any additional stress might fall. Remember, descriptive phrases are
stressed on the second word and set phrases on the first. Use one of your
colored markers to indicate the stressed words. Second, go through the second
paragraph and mark the remaining stressed words. Third, put slash marks where you
think a short pause is appropriate in the third paragraph. Fourth, in the last
paragraph, change T's to either a D or a held T as needed. Listen as the speaker
reads the paragraph. Ignorance on Parade. You say you don't know a proton from a
croton? Well, you're not the only one. A recent nationwide survey funded by the
National Science Foundation shows that fewer than six percent of American adults
can be called scientifically literate. The rest think that DNA is a food additive,
Chernobyl is a ski resort, and radioactive milk can be made safe by boiling.